Finding Aid for the Jon Krampner Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Jon Krampner Papers
1930’s-1960’s
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0882
2.94 linear feet
The original provenance of these papers is kept intact. The order closely reflects the chapter outline of Mr. Krampner’s biography of Fred Coe. Numbers in parenthesis show the pagination and number of additional pages in each folder.
- “A”
  - London (Box 1, File 1, Folder 1)
  - empty (Box 1, File 1, Folder 1)
  - empty (Box 1, File 1, Folder 2)
  - empty (Box 1, File 1, Folder 3)
  - Paddy Chayefsky (1) (Box 1, File 1, Folder 4)
  - Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. (2) (Box 1, File 1)
  - ‘Marty’ at LACMA, March 8, 1991 (4-5) (Box 1, File 1)
  - David Shaw (6-9) (Box 1, File 1)
  - Delbert Mann (10-16) (Box 1, File 1)
  - Tad Mosel (17-25) (Box 1, File 1)
  - empty (Box 1, File 2, Folder 5)
  - empty (Box 1, File 2, Folder 6)
  - Laurie Coe (1-22 and 25-46) (Box 1, File 2, Folder 7)
  - Eleanor Cogbill (1-69) (Box 1, File 3, Folder 8)
  - Edward Colton (1-6) (Box 1, File 4, Folder 9)
  - Stephen A. Flynn (1-6) (Box 1, File 4, Folder 10)
  - Horton Foote (1-2) (Box 1, File 4, Folder 11)
  - Cecil Jones (1) (Box 1, File 4, Folder 12)
  - Delbert and Ann Mann (1-18 plus 3 pages) (Box 1, File 4, Folder 13)
  - Pier Mapes (1-5) (Box 1, File 4, Folder 14)
  - J. P. Miller (1-7) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 15)
  - Priscilla Morgan (1-4) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 16)
  - Tad Mosel (1-7 plus 2 pages) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 17)
  - Harry Muheim (1-8 plus 1 page) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 18)
  - Arthur Penn (1-11) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 19)
  - David Shaw (1-3) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 20)
  - Ira Skutch (1-10 plus 1 page) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 21)
  - Pat Weaver (1-6) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 22)
  - Empty (Box 1, File 5, Folder 23)
  - Robert Lantz (1-2) (Box 1, File 5, Folder 24)
  - Empty (Box 1, File 5, Folder 25)
- “B”
  - ‘Total TV’ Listings [Also: Prime Time Complete] (1-32) (Box 1, File 6, Folder 1)
  - Dramatic Anthology Shows of the ‘50’s (1-4) (Box 1, File 6, Folder 2)
  - Screening Notes [TV Shows] ( 36 pages) (Box 1, File 7, Folder 3)
  - UCLA Film and Television Archive [and others] (17 pages) (Box 1, File 7, Folder 4)
  - New York Times Articles (2 pages printed from Microfilm) (Box 1, File 8, Folder 6)
  - Actors’ Credits (6 pages) (Box 1, File 8, Folder 6)
  - Writers’, Directors’ Firsts [Also: Reading Notes of Philcos] ( 1-33) (Box 1, File 8, Folder 7)
  - Articles by Fred Coe (3-7, 8-10) (Box 1, File 9, Folder 8)
  - Articles about Fred Coe (25 pages) (Box 1, File 9, Folder 9)
  - TV Guide Articles (12 pages) (Box 1, File 9, Folder 10)
  - Statistics (3 pages) (Box 1, File 10, Folder 11)
  - Reviews (8 pages) (Box 1, File 10, Folder 12)
  - Authors’ Notes [TV Play Writers prefaces] (1-45) (Box 1, File 10, Folder 13)
  - Irwin A. Cantor (1-2) (Box 1, File 11, Folder 14)
  - Empty (Box 1, File 11, Folder 15)
  - Empty (Box 1, File 11, Folder 16)
  - Empty (Box 1, File 11, Folder 18)
  - Empty (Box 1, File 11, Folder 18)
  - Empty (Box 1, File 11, Folder 19)
  - Jane Deacy (1-2) (Box 1, File 11, Folder 20)
  - Dominick Dunne (1-4) (Box 1, File 11, Folder 21)
  - Larry Elikann (1-9) (Box 1, File 11, Folder 22)
  - Paddy Chayefsky (5 pages) (Box 1, File 11, Folder 23)
  - Julian Claman (1 page) (Box 1, File 11, Folder 24)
  - “Marty” Ending Controversy (3 pages) (Box 1, File 11, Folder 25)
  - Sundry Philco-Goodyear from S.M.S.W. (22 pages) (Box 1, File 12, Folder 26)
  - Shaun Considine (3 pages) (Box 1, File 12, Folder 27)
  - (c-31)- Fred Coe Specific [Post-Hoc Variety Clips] (9 pages) (Box 1, File 13, Folder 31)
  - (c-32)- Ratings [Post-Hoc Variety Clips] (3 pages) (Box 1, File 13, Folder 32)
  - (c-33)- The Blacklist [Post-Hoc Variety Clips] (9 pages) (Box 1, File 13, Folder 33)
  - (c-34)- General Stuff [Post-Hoc Variety Clips] (34 pages) (Box 1, File 13, Folder 34)
- “C”
  - Horton Foote (1-16 and 1a-1j) (Box 2, File 1, Folder 1)
  - Empty (Box 2, File 1, Folder 2)
  - Jay Jackson (1-2) (Box 2, File 1, Folder 3)
  - Phyllis Jenkins (1-13) (Box 2, File 1, Folder 4)
  - Adrienne Luraschi (1-8) (Box 2, File 2, Folder 5)
  - Delbert Mann (1-38 plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 2, Folder 6)
  - E. G. Marshall (1-4 plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 2, Folder 8)
  - Walter Matthau (1-2 plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 3, Folder 8)
  - J. P. Miller (1-2 and a-c plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 3, Folder 9)
  - Priscilla Morgan (1-4) (Box 2, File 3, Folder 10)
  - Bill Nichols (1-27 plus 1 page and booklet on St. Maarten) (Box 2, File 3, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Penn (1-4 and a-e) (Box 2, File 4, Folder 12)
  - Eva Marie Saint (1-4 plus 3 pages) (Box 2, File 4, Folder 13)
  - David Shaw (1-15) (Box 2, File 4, Folder 14)
  - Ira Skutch (1-16) (Box 2, File 4, Folder 15)
  - Empty (Box 2, File 5, Folder 16)
  - O. (Orland) Tamburri ( 1-6) (Box 2, File 5, Folder 17)
  - Eli Wallach (1-2) (Box 2, File 5, Folder 18)
  - Pat Weaver [Sylvester L. Weaver, Jr.] (1-6 plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 5, Folder 19)
  - John Bloch (1-4) (Box 2, File 5, Folder 20)
  - Thomas Phipps (1-6 plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 5, Folder 21)
  - Mike Dann (1-3) (Box 2, File 5, Folder 22)
  - N. Richard Nash (1-6) (Box 2, File 5, Folder 23)
  - Rod Steiger (1-6) (Box 2, File 6, Folder 24)
  - Eileen Heckart (1-5) (Box 2, File 6, Folder 25)
  - Aneta Conseaut (1) (Box 2, File 6, Folder 26)
  - Nancy Marchand (1-3) (Box 2, File 6, Folder 27)
  - Screening Notes (16-19 plus 17 pages) (Box 2, File 6, Folder 28)
  - Screening Notes (1-9) (Box 2, File 6, Folder 29)
  - Post-Hoc Outline and Notes (1-22 and 1-44) (Box 2, File 7, Folder 30)
  - Milt Myers (1-9) (Box 2, File 7, Folder 31)
  - Walter Bernstein (Box 2, File 7, Folder 32)
- “D”
  - ULS Listings (Union List of Serials) (2 Pages) (Box 2, File 8, Folder 1)
  - Moviegoing (1-6) (Box 2, File 8, Folder 2)
  - Chronicles (1-3 plus 8 pages) (Box 2, File 8, Folder 3)
  - The Great White Way (1-5 plus 3 pages) (Box 2, File 8, Folder 4)
  - FC TV Shows (1-2 plus 12 pages) (Box 2, File 8, Folder 5)
  - Reviews (1-47) (Box 2, File 8, Folder 6)
  - Coe-Specific News (1-15) (Box 2, File 9, Folder 7)
  - Birth of a Medium (1-51 plus 2 pages) (Box 2, File 9, Folder 8)
  - John Royal (1-9 plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 9, Folder 9)
  - Exec. Bios (1-11 plus 1 page) (Box 2, File 10, Folder 10)
  - Thinkers Thinking (1-16) (Box 2, File 10, Folder 11)
  - Albert Abramson (1-3 plus 6 pages) (Box 2, File 10, Folder 12)
  - Empty- Alice Coe (Transferred to Alice book) (Box 2, File 10, Folder 13)
  - Ed Herlihy (1-2) (Box 2, File 10, Folder 14)
  - Empty- Adna Karns (Transferred to Ch.2 book) (Box 2, File 10, Folder 15)
  - Don Pike (1-21) (Box 2, File 10, Folder 16)
  - Eva Marie Saint (1-2) (Box 2, File 11, Folder 17)
  - Ira Skutch (1-18) (Box 2, File 11, Folder 18)
  - Growth of NBC Network (1-5) (Box 2, File 11, Folder 19)
  - “Television Production Problems”—“Problems in the Studio” by FC (Also: John Royal Introduction) (17 pages) (Box 2, File 11, Folder 20)
  - Post Hoc (Chapter 3 Post-Hoc Outline)(1-3 plus 10 pages) (Box 2, File 11, Folder 21)
- “E”
  - Fred Coe News (Including First Stable Info. ‘48-’51 FC Articles, Palmetto Doc Letter)(1-18) (Box 2, File 12, Folder 1)
  - Philco News (1-35) (Box 2, File 12, Folder 2)
  - Philco Reviews (1-83) (Box 2, File 12, Folder 3)
  - NBC and NBT News (1-3) (Box 3, File 1, Folder 4)
  - Rise of Original TV Scripts (1-16) (Box 3, File 1, Folder 5)
  - Rise of Dramatic Anthologies (1-12) (Box 3, File 1, Folder 6)
  - Studio One (1-24) (Box 3, File 1, Folder 7)
  - Kraft(1-5 plus 4 pages) (Box 3, File 1, Folder 8)
  - Robert Montgomery (1-8) (Box 3, File 1, Folder 9)
  - Ed Sullivan (1-10 plus 1 page) (Box 3, File 1, Folder 10)
  - Ratings (1-10) (Box 3, File 2, Folder 11)
  - General News (1-20) (Box 3, File 2, Folder 12)
  - Herbert Swope, Jr. (1-5) (Box 3, File 2, Folder 13)
  - Bud Yorkin (1-3 plus 2 pages) (Box 3, File 2, Folder 15)
  - Hildy Parks (1-2) (Box 3, File 2, Folder 16)
  - Rhoda (Rosenthal) Herrick (1-10) (Box 3, File 2, Folder 17)
- “F”
  - NYT, TNR Articles (2-7 plus 2 pages) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 1)
  - Philco Screening Notes (1-15 plus 3 pages) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 2)
  - Empty- Alice Coe (moved to “Alice”) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 3)
  - Empty- Joyce (Beeler) Coe (plus: Osborner Centric bios) (Moved to “Joyce” book ) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 4)
  - Jack Coffey (unmarked) (1-6 plus 2 pages) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 5)
  - Norman Corwin (1) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 6)
  - Empty- Larry Elikann (Box 3, File 3, Folder 7)
  - Charlton Heston (1-2) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 8)
  - Phyllis Adams (Jenkins) (1-10 plus 1 page) (Box 3, File 3, Folder 9)
  - Grace Kelly (1-12) (Box 3, File 4, Folder 10)
  - Adrienne Luraschi (1-7) (Box 3, File 4, Folder 11)
  - Delbert Mann (1-20 plus 18a-18c) (Box 3, File 4, Folder 12)
  - Empty- Thomas Phipps (Transferred to C-21) (Box 3, File 4, Folder 13)
  - Don Pike (1-5) (Box 3, File 4, Folder 14)
  - David Shaw (1-8) (Box 3, File 4, Folder 15)
  - Dick Smith (1-11 plus 1 page) (Box 3, File 5, Folder 16)
  - O. Tamburri (1-3) (Box 3, File 17, Folder 17)
  - Pat Weaver (1-4) (Box 3, File 17, Folder 18)
  - Variety Obits (1-5 plus 1 page) (Box 3, File 17, Folder 19)
  - D. W. Griffith (Includes “Birth of the Movies” Screening Notes) (1-22) (Box 3, File 17, Folder 20)
  - Carol Matthau (1-2) (Box 3, File 6, Folder 21)
  - Adeline (Garner) Shell (1-10) (Box 3, File 6, Folder 22)
  - Nelle (Rahm) Hankinson (1-5) (Box 3, File 6, Folder 23)
  - Arthur Altschul (page 1) (Box 3, File 6, Folder 24)
  - “Van Gohn” Studio Schematic (t “Rm. 517” Mention) (2 pages) (Box 3, File 6, Folder 25)
  - Post- Hoc (Chapter 4 Post-Hoc Outline) (1-16, 1-27 plus 2 pages) (Box 3, File 6, Folder 26)
- “G”
  - Screening Notes (1- 47) (Box 3, File 7, Folder 1)
  - “Mr. Peepers” Articles (24 pages) (Box 3, File 8, Folder 2)
  - “Mr. Paeepers” Reviews (20 Pages) (Box 3, File 8, Folder 3)
  - “Mr. Peepers” Timeline (1-6) (Box 3, File 8, Folder 4)
  - Variety of Obituaries of Wally Cox (6 pages) (Box 3, File 8, Folder 5)
  - Bonino (6 pages) (Box 3, File 9, Folder 6)
  - East Hampton (26 pages) (Box 3, File 9, Folder 7)
  - Max Wilk (1-12) (Box 3, File 9, Folder 8)
  - Empty (Box 3, File 9, Folder 9)
  - Castleman and Podrazik (1-4) (Box 3, File 10, Folder 10)
  - Bob Costello (1-49 plus 6 pages) (Box 3, File 10, Folder 11)
  - Mahlon Fox (1-4) (Box 3, File 11, Folder 12)
  - Everett Greenbaum (1-57 plus 1 page) (Box 3, File 11, Folder 13)
  - Georgiann Johnson (1-10) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 14)
  - Tad Mosel (1 page) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 15)
  - Bill Nichols (1-3 plus 1 page) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 16)
  - Empty (Box 3, File 12, Folder 17)
  - David Swift (1-37 plus 3 pages) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 18)
  - Richard A. R. Pinkham (1 page) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 19)
  - General Stuff (4 pages) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 20)
  - Perry Massey (1 page) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 21)
  - Post-Hoc (12 pages) (Box 3, File 12, Folder 22)
- “H”
  - General (1-21) (Box 3, File 13, Folder 1)
  - Blacklist (1-4) (Box 3, File 13, Folder 2)
  - Decline of New York (1-4) (Box 3, File 13, Folder 3)
  - NBC Management Structure (1-6) (Box 3, File 13, Folder 4)
  - Decline of Anthologies (1-28) (Box 3, File 13, Folder 5)
  - Articles about Fred Coe (1-15) (Box 4, File 1, Folder 6)
  - P-54 Articles and Documents (1-39 plus 3 pages) (Box 4, File 1, Folder 7)
  - Lux Video Theatre (1-5) (Box 4, File 1, Folder 8)
  - Traveling Lady (1-4) (Box 4, File 2, Folder 9)
  - P.S. Reviews and Articles (1-58) (Box 4, File 2, Folder 10)
  - P.S.: Peter Pan (1-37 plus 5 pages) (Box 4, File 3, Folder 11)
  - P.S. Screening Notes (1-13 plus 2 pages) (Box 4, File 3, Folder 12)
  - P.S. Casting Lists (1-7) (Box 4, File 2, Folder 13)
  - Philco ‘54-’55 Reviews and Articles (1-37) (Box 4, File 4, Folder 14)
  - Philco Screening Notes (1-3 plus 2 pages) (Box 4, File 4, Folder 15)
  - P-56 (Reviews and Articles (1-54) (Box 4, File 4, Folder 16)
  - P-56 Screening Notes (1-11 plus 14 pages) (Box 4, File 5, Folder 17)
  - P-56 Casting Lists (1-2) (Box 4, File 5, Folder 18)
  - Variety ’56 Tribute to Fred Coe (1-8) (Box 4, File 5, Folder 19)
  - Horton Foote ( 1-2) (Box 4, File 5, Folder 20)
  - Jerome Robbins (1 page) (Box 4, File 5, Folder 21)
  - Post-Hoc (8 pages) (Box 4, File 5, Folder 22)
- “I”
  - Jane Arthur (1-29) (Box 4, File 6, Folder 1)
  - Everett Chambers (1-5) (Box 4, File 6, Folder 2)
  - Empty (Box 4, File 6, Folder 3)
  - Empty (Box 4, File 6, Folder 4)
  - Mike Dann (1-13 plus 1 page) (Box 4, File 6, Folder 5)
  - Dominick Dunne (1-10 plus 1 page) (Box 4, File 6, Folder 6)
  - Rose Claire Duff (1-2) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 7)
  - Corrine (Corky) Elikann (1-2) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 8)
  - Joe Fox (1-3) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 9)
  - Bob Ginna ( 1-4 plus 2 pages) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 10)
  - Sam Hall (1-8) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 11)
  - A. E. Hotchner (1-7) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 12)
  - Clark Jones (1-4) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 13)
  - Bill Klages ( 1-10) (Box 4, File 7, Folder 14)
  - Delbert Mann (1-25) (Box 4, File 8, Folder 15)
  - J. P. Miller (1-24 plus 1 page) (Box 4, File 8, Folder 16)
  - Priscilla Morgan ( 1-18 plus 1 page) (Box 4, File 8, Folder 17)
  - Tad Mosel (i-iv and 1-27) (Box 4, File 9, Folder 18)
  - Harry Muheim (1-23) (Box 4, File 9, Folder 19)
  - N. Richard Nash (1-7) (Box 4, File 9, Folder 20)
  - Bill Nichols ( 1-6) (Box 4, File 9, Folder 21)
  - Arthur Penn (1-14) (Box 4, File 10, Folder 22)
  - Arnold Schulman (1-6) (Box 4, File 10, Folder 23)
  - David Shaw (1-3) (Box 4, File 10, Folder 24)
  - Ira Skutch (1 page) (Box 4, File 10, Folder 25)
  - Dick Smith (1-4) (Box 4, File 10, Folder 26)
  - David Swift (1-2) (Box 4, File 10, Folder 27)
  - Pat Weaver (1-5) (Box 4, File 10, Folder 28)
  - Gore Vidal (34 pages) (Box 4, File 11, Folder 29)
  - Cecil Smith (1 page) (Box 4, File 11, Folder 30)
  - Joe Bleeden (1-4) (Box 4, File 11, Folder 31)
  - Jeff Hayden (1-3) (Box 4, File 11, Folder 32)
- “J”
  - General Stuff (1-5) (Box 4, File 12, Folder 1)
  - Articles about Fred Coe (1-18) (Box 4, File 12, Folder 2)
  - “Two for the Seesaw” (1-15) (Box 4, File 12, Folder 3)
  - “The Left-Handed Gun” (1-16) (Box 4, File 12, Folder 4)
  - CBS Management Structure (1-2) (Box 4, File 13, Folder 5)
  - Decline of Anthology Drama (1-23) (Box 4, File 13, Folder 6)
  - The Blacklist (1) (Box 4, File 13, Folder 7)
  - Westerns (1-4) (Box 4, File 13, Folder 8)
  - Rise of Hollywood TV (1-3) (Box 4, File 13, Folder 9)
  - “The Red Mill” (2-5) (Box 4, File 13, Folder 10)
  - P-90 Checklists (1-17) (Box 4, File 14, Folder 11)
  - P-90 General (1-20) [Contains some S.M.S.W. Stuff (sec.12)] (Box 4, File 14, Folder 12)
  - P-90 “Plot to Kill Stalin” (1-31) (Box 4, File 14, Folder 13)
  - P-90 Reviews (1-30 plus 6 pages) [Notices of Elaine Man’s Withdrawal from “Journey” J-14, 9a-29e and Ratings for “Bell Tolls I and II” and Competitors J-14, 21a-21b] (Box 5, File 1, Folder 14)
  - P-90 Screening Notes (1-22 plus 1 page) (Box 5, File 1, Folder 15)
  - “The Miracle Worker” (1-16) (Box 5, File 2, Folder 16)
  - Anne Bancroft (1) (Box 5, File 2, Folder 17)
  - Adri Butler (1-5) (Box 5, File 2, Folder 18)
  - Robert Butler (1-4) (Box 5, File 2, Folder 19)
  - Arthur Cantor (1-32) (Box 5, File 2, Folder 20)
  - Charles Cappleman (1-4) (Box 5, File 2, Folder 21)
- “K”
  - Empty (Box 5, File 3, Folder 1)
  - Patty Duke (1-3) (Box 5, File 3, Folder 2)
  - Henry Fonda (9 pages) (Box 5, File 3, Folder 3)
  - Horton Foote (1-2) (Box 5, File 3, Folder 4)
  - John Frankenheimer (1-8 plus 4 pages) (Box 5, File 3, Folder 5)
  - William Gibson (1-23) (Box 5, File 3, Folder 6)
  - Bo Goldman (1-37 plus 7 pages) (Box 5, File 4, Folder 7)
  - Brooks Graham (1-2) (Box 5, File 4, Folder 8)
  - Joe Harris (1-9) (Box 5, File 4, Folder 9)
  - Roger Hirson [?] (1-14) (Box 5, File 5, Folder 10)
  - A. E. Hotchner (1-5) (Box 5, File 5, Folder 11)
  - George Jenkins (1-17) (Box 5, File 5, Folder 12)
  - Phyllis (Adams) Jenkins (1) (Box 5, File 5, Folder 13)
  - Martin Jurow (1-5) (Box 5, File 5, Folder 14)
  - David Karp (1-23) (Box 5, File 6, Folder 15)
  - Delbert Mann (1-26) (Box 5, File 6, Folder 16)
  - Martin Manulis (1-13) (Box 5, File 7, Folder 17)
  - J. P. Miller (1-7 plus 1 page) (Box 5, File 7, Folder 18)
  - Tad Mosel (1-12) (Box 5, File 7, Folder 19)
  - Patricia Neal (2 pages) (Box 5, File 7, Folder 20)
  - Arthur Penn (1-6) (Box 5, File 7, Folder 21)
  - Robert Stewart (1-6) (Box 5, File 7, Folder 22)
  - Porter Van Zandt (1-16) (Box 5, File 7, Folder 23)
  - Robert Wallsten (1-4) (Box 5, File 8, Folder 24)
  - Ethel Winant (1-8 plus 3 pages) (Box 5, File 8, Folder 25)
  - Leslie Stevens (1-7) (Box 5, File 8, Folder 26)
  - S.H.S.W. Period-Relevant Correspondence and Article about Alice (6 pages) (Box 5, File 8, Folder 27)
  - Mayo Simon (1-8) (Box 5, File 8, Folder 28)
  - Post-Hoc (15 pages) (Box 5, File 8, Folder 29)
- “L”
  - Chapter 8 Timeline (3 pages plus 5 transparencies) (Box 5, File 9, Folder 1)
  - Great White Way (1-5 plus 1 page) (Box 5, File 9, Folder 2)
  - Fred Coe Pix B. O. Grosses (1-2) (Box 5, File 9, Folder 3)
  - Fred Coe Articles (1-2) (Box 5, File 9, Folder 4)
  - All The Way Home (1-21) (Box 5, File 9, Folder 5)
  - Gideon (1-11) (Box 5, File 10, Folder 6)
  - A Matter of Position (1-11 plus 1 pages) (Box 5, File 10, Folder 7)
  - A Thousand Clowns (Stage Version) (1-5 plus 2 pages) (Box 5, File 10, Folder 8)
  - Journey to the Day (1-2) (Box 5, File 10, Folder 9)
  - Fiddler on the Roof (1-88) (Box 5, File 11, Folder 10)
  - Xmas in Las Vegas (1-14) (Box 5, File 12, Folder 11)
  - The Miracle Worker (Film Version) (1-30) (Box 5, File 12, Folder 12)
  - A Thousand Clowns (Film Version) (1-48) (Box 5, File 13, Folder 13)
  - This Property is Condemned (1-22) (Box 5, File 13, Folder 14)
  - Empty (Box 5, File 13, Folder 15)
  - Theatre ’62 (1-20) (Box 5, File 14, Folder 16)
  - 14th Annual Emmy Awards (1-2) (Box 5, File 14, Folder 17)
  - The Reporter (1-2 plus 1 page) (Box 5, File 14, Folder 18)
  - Fred Coe’s FCC Testimony (1-10) (Box 5, File 14, Folder 19)
  - Political Stuff (1-18 plus 1 page) (Box 5, File 14, Folder 20)
  - Unproduced Stuff (1-2) (Box 5, File 14, Folder 21)
- “M”
  - Renee Alevy (1 ) (Box 6, File 1, Folder 1)
  - Empty (Box 6, File 1, Folder 2)
  - John Coe (1-40 plus 1 page) (Box 6, File 1, Folder 3)
  - Laurie Coe (1-36) (Box 6, File 1, Folder 4)
  - Laurie and John @ Old Spaghetti Factory (1-17) (Box 6, File 2, Folder 5)
  - Sam Coe (1-7) (Box 6, File 2, Folder 6)
  - Sue Coe (1-19) (Box 6, File 2, Folder 7)
  - Alvin Cooperman (1-5) (Box 6, File 2, Folder 8)
  - Francis Ford Coppola (1) (Box 6, File 3, Folder 9)
  - Horton Foote (1-6) (Box 6, File 3, Folder 10)
  - Herb Gardner (1-16) (Box 6, File 3, Folder 11)
  - Sheldon Harnick (1-5) (Box 6, File 3, Folder 12)
  - David Hays (1-6 plus 3 pages) (Box 6, File 3, Folder 13)
  - Arthur Penn (1) (Box 6, File 4, Folder 14)
  - Sydney Pollack (1-4) (Box 6, File 4, Folder 15)
  - Jason Robards (1) (Box 6, File 4, Folder 16)
  - Ralph Rosenblum (1-23) (Box 6, File 4, Folder 17)
  - Ray Stark (4 pages) (Box 6, File 4, Folder 18)
  - Joseph Stein (1-6) (Box 6, File 5, Folder 19)
  - Ellen Violett (1-13 plus 1 page) (Box 6, File 5, Folder 20)
  - Theodore Sorensen (1-3) (Box 6, File 5, Folder 21)
  - Muheim’s Groucho Article (1-23) (Box 6, File 5, Folder 22)
  - Ira Bernstein (“Fiddler”) (1-3) (Box 6, File 5, Folder 23)
  - Post-Hoc (1-5 plus 9 pages) (Box 6, File 5, Folder 24)
- “N”
  - General Stuff(1-2) (Box 6, File 6, Folder 1)
  - Things Fall Apart (1-13) (Box 6, File 6, Folder 2)
  - Wait Until Dark (1966) (1-10 plus 1 page) (Box 6, File 6, Folder 3)
  - The Final War of Olly Winter (1967) (1-41) (Box 6, File 6, Folder 4)
  - Me, Natalie (1969) (1-22) (Box 6, File 7, Folder 5)
  - Georgy (1970) (1-11 plus 1 page) (Box 6, File 7, Folder 6)
  - All The Way Home (Hallmark, 1971) (1-20) (Box 6, File 7, Folder 7)
  - Unproduced Projects (1-3) (Box 6, File 7, Folder 8)
  - Hurrah, Boys, Hurrah (1-18) (Box 6, File 8, Folder 9)
  - Mab Ashforth (1-12) (Box 6, File 8, Folder 10)
  - Paul Bogart (1-9) (Box 6, File 8, Folder 11)
  - Mike Dann (1-3) (Box 6, File 8, Folder 12)
  - Barbara Dello Joio (Barbara Bocton) (1-17) (Box 6, File 8, Folder 13)
  - Ivan Dixon (1-2 plus 1 page) (Box 6, File 9, Folder 14)
  - Joe Fox (1-4) (Box 6, File 9, Folder 15)
  - Margaret Ginna (1-3) (Box 6, File 9, Folder 16)
  - Peter Hunt (1-7) (Box 6, File 9, Folder 17)
  - Jan (Monkhouse) Jessel (1-25 plus 1 page) (Box 6, File 9, Folder 18)
  - Ann Levack (1-32) (Box 6, File 9, Folder 19)
  - J.P. Miller (1-4) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 20)
  - Tad Mosel (1-7) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 21)
  - Arthur Penn (1-4) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 22)
  - Harry Mark Petrakis (1-10) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 23)
  - Ronald Ribman (1 and 4-11) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 24)
  - Barbara Schultz (1-8) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 25)
  - Yvette Schumer (1-3) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 26)
  - Ellen Violett (1-10) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 27)
  - Susan (Kennaway) Vereker (1-4) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 28)
  - Margaret (Sheffield) Mannoni (1-4) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 29)
  - Patty Duke (1-6) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 30)
  - Post-Hoc (6 pages) (Box 6, File 10, Folder 31)
- “P”
  - Fred Coe General (1-18) (Box 6, File 11, Folder 1)
  - Ecog Correspondence with Fred Coe (1-13) (Box 6, File 11, Folder 2)
  - Fred Coe / Joyce Coe Matrimonial File (1-8) (Box 6, File 11, Folder 3)
  - Death of Fred Coe (1-17) (Box 6, File 11, Folder 4)
  - Fred Coe Obits (1-12) (Box 6, File 12, Folder 5)
  - Fred Coe Posthumous (1-5) (Box 6, File 12, Folder 6)
  - Nightwatch (1-7) (Box 6, File 12, Folder 7)
  - Promenade All (1-8) (Box 6, File 12, Folder 8)
  - Of Men and Women (1-7) (Box 6, File 12, Folder 9)
  - Dance/Band (1-11) (Box 6, File 12, Folder 10)
  - Michele Lee Show (1-6) (Box 6, File 13, Folder 11)
  - In Praise of Love (1-13) (Box 6, File 13, Folder 12)
  - Adkron (1-44 plus 2 pages) [Adams Chronicle] (Box 6, File 13, Folder 13)
  - Miracle Worker ’79 (1-32) (Box 6, File 14, Folder 14)
  - Paul Aaron (1-7) (Box 6, File 14, Folder 15)
  - Alice Coe (1-2) (Box 6, File 14, Folder 16)
  - Bob Costello (1-7) (Box 6, File 14, Folder 17)
  - Sybil Costello (1-2) (Box 6, File 14, Folder 18)
  - Empty (Box 7, File 1, Folder 19)
  - Dan Einstein (1) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 20)
  - George W. George (1-3) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 21)
  - A. E. Hotchner (1-2) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 22)
  - Harvey Jacobs (1-5) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Kassel (1-12) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 24)
  - Ray Katz (1-2) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 25)
  - Delbert Mann 1-5) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 26)
  - Kent McCray (1-4) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 27)
  - Ron Simon (1-3) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 28)
  - Arthur Storch (1-3) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 29)
  - Barnard (“Barney”) Straus (1-3) (Box 7, File 1, Folder 30)
  - Porter Van Zandt (1-9) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 31)
  - Ed Wittstein (1) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 32)
  - Bill Weylock (1-8) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Ronald W. Busuttil (1) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 34)
  - Paul Sparer (1-2) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 35)
  - Silva Mind Control (1-12 plus 1 page) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 36)
  - Stanley Gray (1-5) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 37)
  - Don Petersen (1-4) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 38)
  - Mayo Simon (1-7) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 39)
  - Patty Duke (1-6) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 40)
  - Post-Hoc (7 pages) (Box 7, File 2, Folder 41)
- “Q”
  - Witnesses
    - Charles Coe (1-10) (Box 7, File 3, Folder 1)
    - Vera (Coe) Dawes (1-13) (Box 7, File 3, Folder 2)
    - Leslie Stevens (1) (Box 7, File 3, Folder 3)
    - Kate Wells (1-38 plus 1 page) (Box 7, File 3, Folder 4)
    - “Pappy” (1-7) (Box 7, File 4, Folder 5)
  - Site Files
    - Pre-History (1-2) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut (1 page) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta (1-4) (Box 7, Folder 8)